Finding Aid for John Engler Papers, 1968-2003
Bentley Historical Library, University of Michigan
- Gubernatorial Papers, 1970-2003; 411 linear feet
  - Memorabilia, 1968-2002
    - "Governor Engler's Republican Bandstand" party invitations, and "Republican Bandstand Boogie" CDs for party held during GOP convention in Philadelphia., August 2, 2000 (Box 434)
    - "Detroit 300: Tippy Canoe & Edsel Too," button (Box 434)
    - National Governors' Association "Vision for 2001-2002" State Leadership in the 21st Century. Governor Engler, Chairman of NGA (Box 435)
    - Plans for I-94 Improvements for meeting with May or Kilpatrick of Detroit, April 2002 (Box 435)
    - Engler Family Christmas Card, family boarded in Oldsmobile, waving farewell., 2002 (Box 434)
    - Baseball cap, Michigan Educational Savings Plan (Box 435)
    - Embroidered patch, 25 year reunion Mackinac Island Scout Service Camp, 1977-2001 (Box 434)
    - "Fieger Time" wrench attached to a photograph of Geoffrey Fieger (Box 434)
    - Michigan GOP Jubilee Poster, November 3, 1998 (Box 435)
    - "I'm with Sen. Abraham Bush Cheney Abraham Michigan Delegation Republican National Convention" button, 2000 (Box 434)
    - "Follow Thru is the Key to Victory! The Big Swing.com" button (Box 434)